mayook.com 2010-06-14

# Cool Free Vouchers, Games and Fun

**Privacy Policy**

[Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") created this Web Site Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use Mayook.com (the "Website"), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy.  [Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") respect and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used.

If you have additional questions that are not answered here, please send any questions to: 

**Personal Information**

we pay meticulous attention to your personal privacy thus you can feel free to use [Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") site without giving any personal information or data. Although we will appreciate if you contact us or submit feedback with your name and contact information, you are more than welcome to remain anonymous. If you are willing to provide your personal information, [Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that [Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") obtains from you, but [Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") makes no assurances about its ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration. 

**Business Relationships**

[Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") has links to several Web sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites we linked to.

**Cookies**

[Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com") developed tools to control popup windows and IA (interstitial advertisements) as the purpose of these tools is to minimize the amount of advertisements the user watch with on a given visit to [Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com").

**Mailing List**

If you will join our mailing list, we will keep your email address and any demographics information you volunteer strictly confidential. We will never give or sell your email address or any information about you to anyone else.  

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information that information can be collected and used by others. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your online information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Contact Details**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of [Mayook.com](http://www.mayook.com// "Mayook.com"), you can contact us by sending email to:  [support@mayook.com](mailto:support@mayook.com)
